[
    {
        "front": "とくに",
        "back": "特に \nspecially",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "とくべつ",
        "back": "特別 \nspecial",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "とっきゅう",
        "back": "特急 \nlimited express",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "わかれる",
        "back": "別れる \nto be separated",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "べつべつに",
        "back": "別々に \nseparately",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "くべつ",
        "back": "区別 \nto distinguish",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶんべつ",
        "back": "分別 \nto classify",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "あります",
        "back": "有ります \nto exist",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうめい",
        "back": "有名 \nfamous",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうりょう",
        "back": "有料 \nhave to pay",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "むりょう",
        "back": "無料 \nfree",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "たより",
        "back": "便り \nletter, news",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "べんり",
        "back": "便利 \nconvenient",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふなびん",
        "back": "船便 \nship mail",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうびんきょく",
        "back": "郵便局 \npost office",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "べんり",
        "back": "便利 \nconvenient",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "りえき",
        "back": "利益 \npofit",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "きく",
        "back": "効 \neffect",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "りようする",
        "back": "利用する \nto use",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうり",
        "back": "有利 \nadvantages",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "りし",
        "back": "利子 \ninterest (bank)",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふべん",
        "back": "不便 \ninconvenient",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふあん",
        "back": "不安 \nanxiety",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふそく",
        "back": "不足 \ninsufficient",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふうん",
        "back": "不運 \nunfortunate; bad-luck",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "きる",
        "back": "切る \nto cut",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいせつ",
        "back": "大切 \nimportant",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "きって",
        "back": "切手 \npostage stamp",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんせつ",
        "back": "親切 \nkind",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "もと",
        "back": "元 \nbase / origin",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "げんき",
        "back": "元気 \nhealth",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "がんじつ",
        "back": "元日 \nnew year's day",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "きげんぜん",
        "back": "紀元前 \nBC",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "すき",
        "back": "好 \nlike",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうぶつ",
        "back": "好物 \nfavorite dish",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうい",
        "back": "好意 \naffection",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "いそぐ",
        "back": "急ぐ \nto hurry",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "きゅうに",
        "back": "急に \nsuddenly, immediately",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "きゅうよう",
        "back": "急用 \nurgent business",
        "chapter": "N4 K3"
    }
]